Washington Star 061 061
Stage
Washington Star Records
1852-1982
Stage
061
143 linear feet; 169 boxes
Biographical / Historical
By: Faye Haskins, Photo Librarian, Washingtoniana Division, DC Public Library
The first issue of the Evening Star was published as a four-page daily on December 16, 1852 at 8th and D Streets, NW, Washington, D.C. The daily's founder and first editor was Captain Joseph Borrows Tate, a printer and officer in the Washington militia. Tate believed that Washington newspapers published at the time were mouthpieces for the major political parties. He wanted to publish an independent newspaper "free from party trammels and sectarian influences, [that]… will preserve a strict neutrality" as stated in the newspaper's first edition. Tate sold the paper within six months to William H. Hope and William Douglass Wallach; Wallach became the sole owner by 1854. In its early years the paper fought for city improvements and although its editor was a traditional southern democrat, he and his newspaper supported Lincoln's fight to preserve the Union.
In 1867 Crosby S. Noyes, who began as a Star route agent and then reporter in 1853, became editor and one of five new owners. The other owners were Samuel H. Kauffmann, former Ohio newspaper publisher; George W. Adams, Washington correspondent of the New York World; Alexander R. Shepherd, a D.C. political leader; and Clarence Baker. Baker and Shepherd soon sold their shares to the remaining partners. In the late 19th century the Star championed many civic improvements in D.C., including Governor Alexander Shepherd's public works improvements, despite his administration's scandals, a new free public library, Union Station, and the replacement of Potomac River marshes with the Tidal Basin and Potomac Park. Harry P. Godwin became the newspaper's first city editor in 1881 and by 1890 it had its first associate editor, managing editor, and wire news editor. Members of the Kauffmann and Noyes families, including Theodore Noyes, Thomas Noyes, Fleming Newbold, and Frank B. Noyes, who would become future heirs and leaders at the newspaper, started working as Star reporters beginning in the late 1870s to the 1890s.
In 1881 the Star gave up its second home at 11th and D, site of the old Post Office building, to occupy a building at 11th and Pennsylvania Avenue, The Star also purchased a corner building at the same site and by 1900 Star staff moved into a remodeled corner structure. By 1921 the Star had erected a 10-story annex on the 11th Street side known as the Star building, now an historic architectural landmark in the city. The Star's longtime first President, Samuel H. Kauffmann died in 1906. Crosby S. Noyes, owner-editor, died in 1908. Descendants of the Noyes, Kauffmann, and Adams families continued to own and run the paper until the 1960s. On the Star's 50th anniversary in 1902, 42 reporters covered news for the Star and on March 26, 1905 the newspaper published its first Sunday Star.
In 1937 the Star became the first Washington paper to own a radio station, WMAL, and followed as the first paper to own a television station, WMAL-TV, in 1947. During World War II, four Star reporters covered the news overseas, and it published an overseas edition for GIs. Star editor Theodore W. Noyes died in 1946 and Benjamin McKelway was named the new editor. He had no relationship to the three families (Noyes, Kauffmann, and Adams) that ran the paper for almost 80 years. Frank B. Noyes resigned as Star President in 1948, followed by the brief tenure of Fleming Newbold, and finally selection of Samuel H. Kauffmann, grandson of the original owner, as President in 1949.
In 1952 the Star celebrated its 100th birthday with parties, special publications, and much fanfare. By its 100th anniversary, the Star was characterized by the public as a truly local newspaper that had earned a reputation for emphasizing the coverage of local issues, service to the community, and support of civic causes. In 1959, the Star moved from its historic home to a newly constructed 5-story plant at Second Street and Virginia Avenue, S.E.
By the mid-1960s the Star was considered a conservative paper that, among other issues, opposed Home Rule and supported racial integration; by that time, it also trailed behind the Post in circulation and national reputation. In 1975, a Houston, Texas banker, Joseph L. Albritton bought substantial shares of stock in Star Communications, Inc., which included the newspaper and its affiliated TV and radio stations, from the three controlling families for $28.5 million. The Star's financial troubles, however, continued and in 1978, Albritton sold the Evening Star Newspaper Co. to Time, Inc. for $20 million. Although Time Inc. invested more than $80 million in the newspaper; it ceased operations and published its last issue on August 7, 1981. *
Custodial History
The Washington Post, Katherine A. Daly, and the Washington Star gave custodial rights of the Papers of the Washington Star to the Washingtoniana Division over time from 1993 to 1999. The Post also granted custodial rights to over 1.2 million photographs and over 7 million newspaper clippings from the Star to the Washingtoniana Division.
Scope and Contents
The papers of the Washington Star consist of a variety of material formats. These materials were gathered over 130 years of the newspaper's service to the city of Washington. The materials reflect the day-to-day operations of the Star, the publishing of the newspaper and other materials, the leadership changes of the Star, labor disputes, marketing reports, historical materials, and other topical files and reports.
The types of documents found in this collection include: correspondence, financial records, newsletters, newspapers, clippings, advertising and marketing reports, legal documents, photographs, negatives, slides, scrapbooks, audiocassettes, videocassettes, awards, certificates, and programs.
Business; Evening Star Newspaper Co.; American newspapers
- Series 1: Historic Editions, 1853-1981
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains front pages and entire editions of the Washington Star featuring significant events in the history of the Star, the nation, and Washington, DC.
  - Untitled, 1853-1924 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1934-1957 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1974-1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Series 2: Publications, 1884-1982
  This series contains copies of books, pamphlets, fliers, and other materials published by the Star. Some of the files contain printing invoices and financial records, as well. It also contains published materials used as reference tools by staff. Files are arranged alphabetically by title.
  - 100th Anniversary Birthday Party, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 100 Years of Presidential Elections, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 100 Years of Presidential Elections, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - $403,798,830.74 is Missing: The Trouble at Social Security, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - $403,798,830.74 is Missing: The Trouble at Social Security, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - All About Living in the Washington Area, 1967-1974 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - All About Living in the Washington Area, 1967-1974 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - All About Living in the Washington Area, 1967-1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - All About Living in the Washington Area, 1967-1974 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - All About Living in the Washington Area, 1967-1974 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - All About Living in the Washington Area, 1967-1974 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Almanac - Evening Star, 1884-1888 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Almanac and Handbook - Evening Star, 1896 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Almanac and Handbook - Evening Star, 1897 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - A.M. Extra, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report (Draft), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Annual Reports, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Atomic Years, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Atomic Years, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Beauty in Flowers, 1964-1970 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Beauty in Flowers, 1964-1970 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Beauty in Flowers, 1964-1970 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Brown is Beautiful - Posters, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Building for the Future, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Business and Financial Review, 1975, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Business and Financial Review, 1975, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Calendar - Evening Star, 1884 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Campaign of '48, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Campaign of '52, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Campaign of '56, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Campaign of '68, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Can the US Army Fight?, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Capital Special, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Christmas Cards, Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - City Directories, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Classified Success Ads, Undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Consumer Analysis, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Contests and Giveaways, 1975-1980 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Continuing Study of Newspaper Reading, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Copy Ideas for Selling Real Estate Through…, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Courts vs. Crime, 1965-1969 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Courts vs. Crime, 1965-1969 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Debtor Beware, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Debtor Beware, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Disaster in the Deep, Undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Deutsch, Shea and Evans, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Dry Doomsday, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Dry Doomsday, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Endangered Shoreline, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Energy Section, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Entertain Fashionably, Undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Evening Star, Undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Evening Star: A Century at the Nation's Capital, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Evening Star: Murals, Undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Evening Star: The Story of Its First Century, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Every 27 Minutes, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Every 27 Minutes, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Eyewear Section, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Family Weekly, 1970-1976 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Family Weekly, 1970-1976 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Family Weekly, 1970-1976 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Fashion, 1969-1981 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Fashion, 1969-1981 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Financial Articles, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Fishing Guide - 1958-1960, Undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Fishing Guide - 1958-1960, Undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Fishing Guide - 1958-1960, Undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Fishing Guide- 1958-1960, Undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Food Brokers Association Directory, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Freedom Train, 1962-1963 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - FYI Communications Inc., 1975 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Garden Book, 1951-1976 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Garden Book, 1951-1976 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Garden Book, 1951-1976 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Garden Book, 1951-1976 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Garden Book, 1951-1976 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Garden Book, 1951-1976 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Garden Book, 1951-1976 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Garden Book, 1951-1976 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Garden Book, 1951-1976 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Garden Book, 1951-1976 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Garden Book, 1951-1976 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Get it Straight from the Star, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Get it Straight from the Star, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Get it Straight from the Star, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Get it Straight from the Star, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Get it Straight from the Star, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Get it Straight from the Star, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Get it Straight from the Star, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Growing Up with Newspapers- 1970, Undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Growing Up with Newspapers - 1970, Undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Guide to Effective Classified Advertising, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Help Your Child Succeed in School, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Heroin Trail, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - High Cost of Health, 1959-1970 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - High Cost of Health, 1959-1970 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - High Cost of Health, 1959-1970 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Holocaust in History, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Hole By Hole at Congressional, Undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Home Entertainment Section, 1971-1979 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Home Owner Beware!, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - How Much Home Can You Afford?, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - How Safe is Your House From Burglars?, Undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - How to Get Into College and Finance It Too, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Huber News, 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Indexing Manual, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Information Please Almanac, 1959-1972 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - In Memoriam: JFK, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Inside Football Report, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Inside Straight, 1977-1981 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Inside Straight, 1977-1981 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Inside Straight, 1977-1981 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Inside Straight, 1977-1981 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Inside Straight, 1977-1981 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Insurance Crisis, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - In the Twilight, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Investors Beware, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Jobs for the Jobless, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Legal Register, 1971-1977 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Vince Lombardi: Portrait, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Love Is…, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Mariner to Mars, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Medicare and Social Security Benefits, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Metro…City of Tomorrow, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Metropolitan Washington Board of Trade News, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Money in Your Pocket, Undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Money Lure, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Moon Shot!, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Mortgage Game, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Negro in Washington, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Neighborhood Facilities and Services in the New Southwest, Undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - New Star Building: A Year of Progress, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Boys March, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers' Report on the Action Plan for Downtown, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Nightingale Dilemma, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Nixon Interview, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Our Endangered Shoreline, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Our Growing Suburbs, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Our Victory Garden, 1943-1944 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Our Victory Garden, 1943-1944 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Pocket Atlas of the World, 1887 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Pope in America, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - President's Portfolio, 1963-1973 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Pride of the Star, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Progress, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Real Estate Descriptive Phrases, Undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Real Estate Headline Ideas, Undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Real Estate Headline Ideas - World Selector, Undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Reference Materials, 1968-1975 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Republic, 1879 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - S and P Year-end Stock Guide, 1967-1975 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - S and P Year-end Stock Guide, 1967-1975 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Schools for the '70s, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Sites of War, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Songs About Washington DC, 1924-1972 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Special Report by Frank B. Noyes, 1945 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Star Booklet, 1934 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Star Cartoon Books, 1956-1969 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Star Classified Advertising, 1972-1977 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Star People, 1958-1959 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Star Tour Book, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Stock Guide, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Story of the Washington Star, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Straight from the Washington Star, 1975-1978 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Straight from the Washington Star, 1975-1978 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Straight from the Washington Star, 1975-1978 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Straight from the Washington Star, 1975-1978 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Straight from the Washington Star, 1975-1978 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Straight from the Washington Star, 1975-1978 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Straight from the Washington Star, 1975-1978 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Straight from the Washington Star, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Supermarketplace, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Supersonic Struggle, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Supersonic Struggle, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Telephone Directory, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Tele Vue, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - They Had a Dream, 1969-1971 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - This is Star…Fashion, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Time to Keep, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Trailing the Trotters, Undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Travel Advertising, 1970-1979 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - TV Magazine, 1967-1972 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Used Car Buyer Beware, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Used Car Buyer Beware, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Warren Report, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Wash Account Items, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Washington Capital, 1900 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Washington Facts and Figures, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Washingtonian, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Washington Magazine - Memos, 1970-1973 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Washington Magazine - Memos, 1970-1973 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Washington Magazine - Memos, 1970-1973 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Washington: The Nation's Capital, Undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Washington Star March, 1924-1960 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Washington Star March, 1924-1960 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Weekday/Sunday Advertising, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - What You Can Do About Drugs, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Where Did Your Money Go?, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Where Did Your Money Go?, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Why All Numbers, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - World Almanac, 1973-1978 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - World Almanac, 1973-1978 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - World in Danger, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - World in Danger, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Year End Stock Guide, 1963-1965 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - You and Your Newspaper, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - You and Your Newspaper, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - You Can Get Better Grades, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Your School Newspaper, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Zoning, Rezoning, and…The Big Land Boom, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - The Morning Star, Undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Series 3: Star Index, 1894-1904
  The Star Index is made up of cards containing subject headings indexed from late 19th and early 20th century editions of the Star. Subject headings and names are filed in alphabetical order.
  - Untitled, 1894-1895 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1896-1897 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1898-1899 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1900-1901 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1902-1903 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1904 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Local Transportation Problem as Told by the Card Index of the Evening Star, 1912-1927 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Topical Index to the Evening Star, 1852-1899 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Topical Index to the Evening Star, 1852-1899 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Topical Index to the Evening Star, 1852-1899 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Topical Index to the Evening Star, 1852-1899 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Topical Index to the Evening Star, 1852-1899 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Topical Index to the Evening Star, 1852-1899 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Topical Index to the Evening Star, 1852-1899 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Topical Index to the Evening Star, 1852-1899 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Series 4: Advertising, 1889-1981
  Advertising materials, correspondence, reports, and fliers make up this series of the Star papers. Files are arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - 1889-1952 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - 1928-1950 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - 1934 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - 1940-1945 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - 1940-1945 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Accent Issues, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Accounts Receivable, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Action Guide, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Addy Awards, 1977-1979 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Ad Order Processing Center, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Ad Order Processing Center - Budget, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Ad Processing Center - Bags, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Advertising Adjustments, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Advertising Checking Bureau, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Advertising Club of Metropolitan Washington Inc., 1971-1975 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Advertising Club of Metropolitan Washington Inc., 1971-1975 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Advertising Council, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Advertising News of New York, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Advertising Plans, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - ADW Advertising Co., 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - ADW Advertising Co., 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Agency Presentations, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Air Travelers' Guide, 1970-1973 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - All About Living in the Washington Area, 1972-1974 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - All About Living in the Washington Area, 1972-1974 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - All About Living in the Washington Area, 1972-1974 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - All About Living in the Washington Area, 1972-1974 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Joe L. Allbritton, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - American Cancer Society, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - American Newspaper Publishers Association, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - American Press Institute, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - American Press Institute - Programs, 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - American Security and Trust Co., 1975 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - American University, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - AM Extras, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Jeanne Anderson, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Anne Arundel Times, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Annual Report, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Annual Report, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Antiques, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Apartment and Condominium Section, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - ARTEC (Metro Cable), 1979 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Arts Preview Section, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Automotive, 1971-1975 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Automotive, 1971-1975 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Automotive Advertising, 1976-1980 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Automotive Corporations, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Automotive Presentation, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Automotive - Ford Motor Co., 1972 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Back to School, 1973-1980 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Back to School, 1973-1980 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Barr Realty Inc., 1975 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Bernard Soep Associates Inc., 1978 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Better Business Bureau, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Big 8 Publishers, 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Boat Show, 1969-1974 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Boat Show, 1969-1974 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Book Calendar, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Boston Globe, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Bowling Section, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Bridal, 1971-1981 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Budget, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Burns Productivity Study, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - CENSTAT Project, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Churches, 1969-1980 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Classified, 1975-1981 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Classified, 1975-1981 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Classified, 1975-1981 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Classified- Incentives and Contests, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Classified Ads, 1970-1971 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Classified Ad Count, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Classified Linage, 1969-1975 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Classified Rates, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Classified Section Changes, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Columbia Business Furniture Inc., 1975 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Commerce Clearing House, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Complaints, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Contracts, 1975-1980 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Contracts, 1975-1980 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Conventions and Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Conventions and Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 28, Folder 19)